<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- <rjw.MiscTranslationDef>
		<defName>DesignatorComfortPrisoner</defName>
		<targetClass>rjw.Designator_ComfortPrisoner</targetClass>
		<label>comfort prisoner</label>
		<description>Designate the prisoner as a tool to satisfy everyone's sexual need.</description>
	</rjw.MiscTranslationDef> -->

  <rjw_vatgrown_sex_slave.label>Vat-Grown Sex Slave</rjw_vatgrown_sex_slave.label>
  <rjw_vatgrown_sex_slave.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is made as a sex machine, rather than a human. During [PAWN_possessive] growing period in the factory, [PAWN_pronoun] was taught plenty of social skills and sex skills, just to satisfy various sex demands.</rjw_vatgrown_sex_slave.description>

人造性奴隷
[PAWN_nameDef]はヒトというよりは肉便器として造られました。ファクトリーで成長している間に、様々な肉欲を満たすためだけに十分な社交術と性技術を[PAWN_pronoun]は躾けられました。

  <rjw_feisty.label>Feisty Nymph</rjw_feisty.label>
  <rjw_feisty.description>[PAWN_nameDef] struts around the colony like a conqueror examining a newly annexed territory. You try to focus on your work but [PAWN_pronoun] won't let you.\n
"I heard what you said about me!" [PAWN_pronoun] accuses. You didn't say anything about [PAWN_objective]. [PAWN_pronoun] knows that. "Wanna fight?" [PAWN_pronoun] challenges. You already know what [PAWN_pronoun] means: a few minutes of play wrestling and then you take [PAWN_objective], or, if you hesitate, [PAWN_pronoun] takes you.\n
Though [PAWN_nameDef] can be hard to get along with you've come to appreciate how [PAWN_pronoun]'s more practical than the others.\n
You explain to [PAWN_objective], "See these things here? They need to be over there" and "Those people are trying to kill us, so let's kill them first." [PAWN_pronoun] listens, and does what is necessary.</rjw_feisty.description>

怒れるニンフ（x 高度な作業、看護、動物の世話、アート、清掃）

  <rjw_curious.label>Curious Nymph</rjw_curious.label>
  <rjw_curious.description>Hold the covering plate back and place the actuator in slot C. Line the rod up. No, that won't do, it needs to be perfect. Now pop the JC-444 chip in place.\n
Solder the orange wire to pin #16 and the striped wire to pin #5.\n
Suddenly, there [PAWN_pronoun] is. You aren't surprised to see [PAWN_nameDef], you just didn't hear [PAWN_objective] approach. By now you're used to it.\n
You continue your work in silence as [PAWN_pronoun] hovers over you, her large eyes fixated on the rapid, rythmic, deliberate motions of your hands.</rjw_curious.description>

カバープレートを備えておき、アクチュエータをスロットCに置く。ロッドを上に向ける。うまくいかない、完璧にしないと。急いでJC-444チップを取り付ける。
オレンジのワイヤーを16番ピンに、ストライプのワイヤーを5番ピンにハンダ付け。
突然、彼女はそこにいた。あなたはJANEを見て驚くことはありません、あなたは彼女のアプローチを聞いていないだけです。今ではもう慣れていた。
彼女があなたの上に乗っている間、あなたの仕事は静かに続き、あなたの手の素早く、リズミカルで、意図的な動きに彼女の大きな目は釘付けになっている。

好奇心ニンフ（建築、工芸）（x 雑用、戦闘、看護、動物の世話、アート、料理、農業、採掘）

  <rjw_tender.label>Tender Nymph</rjw_tender.label>
  <rjw_tender.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has a pair of charming eyes, and [PAWN_possessive] voice is soft and sweet. Due to [PAWN_possessive] previous nurse job, [PAWN_pronoun] tends people quite well.\n
[PAWN_pronoun]'s crouched in the corner, hands over [PAWN_possessive] ears and tears in [PAWN_possessive] eyes. You don't understand, then you notice it: the distant sound of the pained squeals of pigs being slaughtered.</rjw_tender.description>

柔和なニンフ（x 高度な作業、戦闘、動物の世話、アート、運搬）
[PAWN_nameDef]は魅力的な目と柔らかくて甘い声をしている。以前看護師をしていたおかげか、人当たりが良い。\n
[PAWN_pronoun]は部屋の隅にうずくまり、耳をふさぎ涙をこぼした。屠殺される豚の悲鳴に気づいても、あなたはそれを理解できなかった。

  <rjw_chatty.label>Chatty Nymph</rjw_chatty.label>
  <rjw_chatty.description>No one can be more loquacious than [PAWN_nameDef]. [PAWN_pronoun] has a flexible tongue, a sharp mind, and hot lips.</rjw_chatty.description>

おしゃべりニンフ（x　雑用、高度な作業、戦闘、看護、動物の世話、アート）
[PAWN_nameDef]ほど饒舌な者は居ないでしょう。[PAWN_pronoun]はよく舌が回り、抜け目なく、艶やかな唇を持っています。

  <rjw_broken.label>Broken Nymph</rjw_broken.label>
  <rjw_broken.description>Maybe [PAWN_nameDef] suffered some terrible things, [PAWN_pronoun] looks rather emaciated, and no one wants to speak with [PAWN_objective].\n
[PAWN_pronoun] only behaves a bit vivaciously while staring at some rod-like stuffs.</rjw_broken.description>

壊れたニンフ（アート）（x　高度な作業、戦闘、看護、動物の世話、清掃）


</LanguageData>